"My Secret Vampire"
(Episode 2)
What the... Was it a dream?
Hey, hey! Let go of me...
What the hell are you doing?
I was just saying hello
to a human I'd never seen before.
Don't get the wrong idea.
Do you usually say
hello to sleeping humans?
Occasionally?
What?
Were you waiting up for me?
As if.
How disappointing.
But who's that guy?
He's kinda cute.
Cute, my ass.
What does going to college
have to do with living with that guy?
Practice, I guess.
Ugh! I really don't get
what Sis is thinking.
But she always has your
best interests at heart.
Whatever, let's just
tough it out for a month.
So you'd better not cause any trouble.
We'll see how you do.
Here, drink up.
Isn't this all you drink when you're sick?
How did you know I was sick?
Your sister told me.
Ugh! Why does my sister always contact you?
Sorry for the trouble.
I don't mind.
I went out for a bit since I heard it was
overcast, but I still couldn't get the book...
This?
You...
This is a first edition!
How did you get your hands on this?
Do you want to give me a kiss?
Have you ever been hit with a book?
So he does know how to smile.
Hello! I'm Han Dongha.
I just moved in today.
Oh.
I'm Kang Seonjae.
You were sleeping just now, weren't you?
I dozed off.
I was probably so tired
I had sleep paralysis.
By the way, Seonjae...
No, that's not right.
Mr. Seonjae...
How should I address you...
Well...
Just call me 'hyung, ' it's easier.
Okay, Seonjae-hyung.
But...
Hyung, you're really handsome.
I knew it.
You've got good taste.
Enough chit-chat, go to sleep.
Huh?
What were you doing with that guy?
Isn't he cute?
What, are you jealous?
I hear human blood is delicious.
And a human just happened to walk right in.
This must be a sign from God.
However...
Do you remember the
Romanian precepts we learned?
I think I've forgotten everything...
Rule number one.
Do not harm humans.
And do not reveal your identity.
First, bite the jugular vein.
You must only drink a moderate amount.
If you drink too much...
you risk losing your senses.
Eligibility for feeding depends
on height, weight, and pulse.
Jeez, there are so many rules!
Just reading this will take all night.
Should I wait for Seonjae and ask him?
- Or should I just go ask Juwon now...
- No way, not Juwon! That guy...
Wow, this is a work of art.
My family lives in the
countryside, so I couldn't print it out.
How rural are we talking?
Oh... deep in the mountains.
- So you came to Seoul by yourself for school?
- Yes.
So where are you living now?
I'm staying in a shared apartment nearby.
I see.
Oh, but by the way...
Why did you apply here of all places?
Because I've had a sweet
tooth ever since I was a kid.
Mm, okay.
So then...
When can you start working?
That's the most important thing.
I can start right now.
The money for the umbrella.
No, no, that's not what I meant.
Let's not get involved
with each other again.
(Lee Juwon)
Why did you suddenly move
Han Dongha's room here?
Could it be that Juwon is
afraid we'll bite Dongha?
So he wants to keep an eye on us?
Could it be because of me?
You already bit him?!
I didn't get a taste, though.
Seonjae, let us have him this time.
It's the first time for all of us.
Still, there's no need
to move his room, right?
Can't we just have a little
sip while living together?
He's always hated that kind of thing.
It's not like you don't know that.
Seonjae.
But what does human blood taste like?
Is it really that good?
Of course.
Is it really different from blood packs?
Hey! You can't even compare the two.
You're so bold.
What if you get caught?
The moment your fangs pierce the flesh...
a sweet aroma instantly fills the air.
The fresh, cool blood...
- flows down my esophagus.
- What's flowing down someone's esophagus?
A gift to celebrate your first day of work.
Share it with your roommates.
That's right! Even if it's only for a
month, you shouldn't feel so uncomfortable.
I'm back.
Huh?
Why have my things been moved out?
What are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
We're moving your things.
Who said you could do that?
If you hate me, you could've just told me.
Why resort to such a cowardly tactic?
What?
Didn't you say not to invade my privacy?
And yet you barge into someone else's room.
Do you think you're the landlord?
- I think you're misunderstanding something...
- I'll leave on my own in a month.
So...
you don't need to worry.
What are you guys doing?
Why is it so tense in here?
Exactly.
I guess I shouldn't have interfered.
Dongha.
We decided to move
your room to the first floor.
Didn't you see the message?
A message?
Yeah, the first floor is
more spacious and better.
Um...
I'm sorry.
I thought you didn't like me.
So I misunderstood.
I want to get closer to you!
Even though it's only for a short month...
we are living under
the same roof, after all.
This place...
is not your home.
There he goes again.
He might say that, but...
he also had your best interests at
heart when he moved your room.
Don't take it to heart.
My best interests?
Juwon probably thought it wasn't good
for you to sleep alone on the second floor.
If you look closely, you'll see...
Juwon is actually the most human among us.
Most human... him?
Yeah.
You're just saying that
because you two are close, right?
Do we look like we're close?
Yes.
Last time I saw you two
together, you looked very close.
Anyway...
you two should stop fighting and get along.
Okay.
How did you slice the tomatoes so well?
Did you take lessons?
But...
we can't eat this kind of stuff.
Still, it's the thought that counts.
Did he put something in this?
Huh?
This is delicious!
Really?
Um...
I made some toast.
I've already eaten.
That was a pretty half-hearted refusal.
The bathroom's clean.
Sigh... When will I ever
finish cleaning this place...
You don't look like
someone who likes books.
What do I look like then?
Done staring?
When was I staring?
I was talking about the book.
And in the future...
don't touch my things.
What's his problem? So annoying.
Wow! It's the cleanest it's ever been.
I feel like my chronic rhinitis is cured.
Cold-blooded... No, that's
not it. He's not even human.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
I don't know if this is
the right time to ask, but...
Forgive my asking, but...
how much do you weigh?
So we're screwed, right?
According to the rules, he
doesn't meet the criteria for feeding.
Looks that way.
Ugh, that Oghwi.
I knew this would happen. Seriously!
So this is what they mean
by 'so close, yet so far.'
And I was so looking forward to it.
I've been barely getting
by on expired blood packs!
And all for prey we can't even feed on.
Well then...
Let's just kick him out of the house.
Okay?
That might be for the best.
Let's keep him.
I kind of like him, actually.
So...
Let's feed him well and make sure he rests.
Let's raise him.
"My Secret Vampire"